<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chorus Project Updates (Draft)</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://tundra.github.io/chorus-updates/draft/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://tundra.github.io/chorus-updates/draft/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 11:35:39 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 11:35:39 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Chorus Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Remember that time you came across a project to create a new terminal called &lt;a href=&quot;http://c7n.p5r.org/chorus&quot;&gt;Chorus&lt;/a&gt;, maybe a while ago, and you signed up to get project updates? Well, here’s a project update.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s new is that I’ve created a blog, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.undra.org/chorus/blog/&quot;&gt;Chorus Console Blog&lt;/a&gt;, where I’ll be posting about the project. The first post is light on details, it’s an introduction, but I have some more detailed posts planned. Future topics include the underlying data model, useful tools you can build on top of that model, and the myriad challenges you encounter when you want to replace the dos prompt on windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That last point incidentally is what I’ve been working on for the last few weeks. I want chorus to work across platforms and on windows that means that it must be a replacement for the dos prompt. Replacements do already exist but they’re subject to many of the same restrictions as the dos prompt itself. That’s not going to work for what I have in mind. Last year I prototyped an approach with fewer restrictions and now I’m working on a full, solid implementation. It’s hairy but it’s also super exciting because of what I’ll be able to do once it works. The image I have in my head is a terminal on windows that looks just like the dos prompt – until you resize the window and the text reflows. That’s actually going to be possible!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll write more about that on the blog. For now you can go there and read the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.undra.org/chorus/blog/2015/12/01/chorus-a-new-kind-of-terminal/&quot;&gt;first post&lt;/a&gt;. And if you have any thoughts about how to make terminals better I’d love to hear from you, either on the mailing list, chorus-discuss@googlegroups.com, or you can reach me directly by responding to this email.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 11:34:37 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://tundra.github.io/chorus-updates/draft/2015/12/02/a-chorus-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tundra.github.io/chorus-updates/draft/2015/12/02/a-chorus-blog.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
